<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>

    TERMS AND CONDITIONS

    This Terms and Conditions Agreement outlines the responsibilities and expectations between Enterprise and C-Verde App regarding the promotion of each other’s products and applications.

    1.	C-Verde
    C-Verde is an application that provide an accessible app that enables individuals to measure their carbon footprints, gain insights into their environmental impact, receive actionable recommendations for reducing emissions, and receive vouchers for challenges/tasks.

    2.	Purpose

    2.1	Both Parties agree to promote each product/application to meet mutual sustainability goals and enhance market reach.

    3.	Scope
    3.1 Enterprise and C-Verde App will promote each other’s products and applications through various marketing channels, including events, campaigns, and promotional materials.
    3.2 Both parties are responsible for providing feedback on the effectiveness of marketing efforts to ensure continuous improvement.
    3.3 The agreement outlines specific benefits for both Enterprise and C-Verde App, including discounts, challenges, and rewards to incentivize consumer participation and increase product exposure.
    3.4 Any promotional content must be consistent with C-Verde’s mission of promoting sustainability and reducing carbon footprints.
    3.5 Both parties are bound by confidentiality agreements to protect sensitive and proprietary information shared during the collaboration.
    3.6 In case of negative publicity or marketing issues, both parties will communicate immediately and collaborate on crisis management to protect the reputations of both brands.

    4.	Restrictions
    4.1 The agreement is limited to promotional activities and does not extend to other aspects such as financial transactions, product development, or joint operations. The responsibilities of both Enterprise and C-Verde App are restricted to marketing efforts and providing feedback on these efforts.
    4.2 Both parties agree that their liabilities are limited to the scope of promotional activities and will not be held liable for any indirect, incidental, or consequential damages arising from the collaboration, except in cases of gross negligence or willful misconduct.
    4.3. Enterprise agrees to indemnify and hold harmless C-Verde from any claims, damages, or liabilities arising from the issuance or redemption of vouchers.

    5.	Duration
    5.1 This Agreement will become effective on February 24, 2025, and will remain in effect until May 26, 2025.

    6.	Benefits
    6.1 For Enterprise:
    6.1.1 Enterprise can get noticed by more people who care about the environment.
    6.1.2 Offering vouchers can get customers more interested and loyal to the brand.
    6.1.3 Stand out from other enterprise.
    6.1.4 Good community Image.

    7.	Voucher Details
    7.1 First 50 registrants will receive a discount of ₱10 off their purchase.
    7.2 First 20 participants to complete a 15-day challenge will earn a voucher for ₱20 off their next purchase.
    7.3 First 5 user to finish the 30/31day challenge will receive two free products.

    8.	Termination
    9.1 Either party may terminate this Agreement by providing written notice to the other party. If either party decides to terminate the Agreement, they will be required to pay a penalty of 2,000 pesos.

    9.	Amendments
    10.1 Any amendments to this Agreement must be made in writing and signed by both Parties.


    10.	Contact Us
    Fb:
    Email:





    IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the Parties have executed this Terms and Conditions Agreement as of the date below.

    Signed:


    __________________
    General Manager
    Enterprise Name
    Date: _____________

    Ameer Viktur Castillo
    Project Manager
    C-Verde Application
    Date:_____________

</resources>